[{"answer": "No, I'm not running the marathon.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "You're not running this marathon yourself are you?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think for one thing.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "Tell me why you're doing this?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "Well I think, you know, I don't if I like using the word reduces but it brings us to our most commonality of spirit.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "What is it about the human spirit you think that reacts in such a remarkable way to terrible natural disasters?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "You must be very proud of him?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Yes, I went up and watch them train and it was beyond -- you asked me earlier was I going to run in the marathon, all you had to do is be there and watch them train and let them do it.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "I mean it make you -- it must be a big adventure for them to come and do this?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Pamela Anderson's a force of nature.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "There is a rumor that Pamela Anderson might be running with them, is that true?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "I was in Port Prince and my first reaction was that I assumed that it had been something that would be called a terrorist attack.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "And what was your reactions with all that?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "In effect, I think that a legitimate whistleblower is one who is the curator of the information that they're distributing.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "Is he a bit of both?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "Very nosy?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "I don't it.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "What would you have got to say?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "I don't think so, not that I've ever seen.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Really, really ever been on film?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "I haven't worked with her, no.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "Have you ever actually worked with her?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "ENN: I know and I think she's lovely but I haven't.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "Would you like to?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "If I knew, I'd be doing it.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "So what makes her so special?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "That's not right.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Seriously?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Where has been all of this, you know, you know, from - Nicholson and De Niro and Marlin and yeah.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Who are the ones that actually feel slightly in awe?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "He is, he is my American brother.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "... people like Ted Cruz?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "I met him on several occasions with -- I didn't know him well.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Did you not?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "My opinion is that we notice them because they're in that business.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "What do you say to young people who want to get in to the Hollywood business and may be even their parents who are going to put their kids into this cauldron?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "That's -- he's exactly right.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "What would you think about?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Well, he was the big brother I never had quite honestly.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "What is your overview of that relationship?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "We discussed everything, you know what I mean, and it was literally like a big brother, little brother relationship where we've talked about everything, I would talk about the abuse that I endured in school which is also in the book, the abuse with my parents and also the difficulties of having to go to work everyday instead of being able to play.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Was he helpful in that sense?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "Thank God.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "I mean does part of you Corey feel, fortunate to still be alive?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "I do it brilliantly but I can't cook anything else so this is like a little God send that's arrived because it's packed full of simple recipes for idiots like me, right?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "I don't believe you're hopeless.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "I mean for someone who's hopeless like me, what is the simple way to be a good cook?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "No, he doesn't.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Does your other half cook for you?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "EINFELD: But he's actually so obsessed with this book and the fact that you can take something and problem solve.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Never?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "We have chicken wings, which I'm very, very excited about for you.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "So talk me through what we have here?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "I do like chicken wings.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Do you like chicken wings?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "It's the First Chili and secondly...", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "What do you mean not bad?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "You and I, right?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "I drink wine when I cook.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Do you crack jokes as you're cooking?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "I think Jerry is funnier than me.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Who's funny, you or Jerry?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "That was good for you.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Who makes you laugh more?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "I definitely make him laugh, which is really nice and you have that experience when we run into each other in Los Angeles and you made him laugh.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "ORGAN: Who makes you laugh more?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Anyone from history, from modern times?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "I would love Eleanor Roosevelt, the Beatles, -- little Edie and big Edie.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Who would your dream dinner party be?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "My husband.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Who would that be?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "(Inaudible), of course.", "docId": "131028pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Obviously, really?", "qSentId": 604}]